FAIRUZ SAIFY RAFIN

MAJOR IN MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEM (MIS)

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name ... Fairuz Saify Rafin
Date of birth ... 12th Sep 1996

Address ... 23/21 Tajmahalroad, Mohammadpur, Dhaka.

Mobile ... +8801823783232 Email ... rafin2378@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile ... http://www.linkedin.com/in/fairuz-saify

PROFILE

To employ my knowledge and experience with the intention of securing a professional career with an opportunity for challenges and career advancement, while using my professional, academic and extracurricular knowledge to gain new skills and experience.

JOB EXPERIENCE

Business Operations Executive

CodeSmith Tech Ltd.

September 2019 – Present

- Scope of Activities
 - Business Process Improvement
 - Office Administration and Management
 - Dynamic Information Management (Both Physical and Digital Information)
 - Accounting, Taxation and Finance Maintenance
 - · Dealing with Client and Client Transaction
 - Working as HR: Employee Management, Payroll handle, Recruitment Process

Kinbanaki.xyz a startup ecommerce site and an umbrella company of CodeSmith Tech Ltd.

- Scope of Activities
 - Worked with all sort of preparatory activities.
 - · New business infrastructure
 - Business process implementation and improvement
 - · Worked with the Kinbanaki crew, from recruitment to strategical planning and analyzing

Business Intern

CodeSmith Tech Ltd.

• June 2019- August 2019

Worked as Content Writer

Fine Answer Student Consultancy

- Prepared reports for different international educational organizations and individual,.
- Worked as outsourcer



OTHER EXPERIENCE AND EXTRA-CURRICULAIR ACTIVITIES

Google Analytics Certificate

Google Analytics Academy

- Online Course, scored 98%
- Certificate link

https://analytics.google.com/analytics/academy/certificate/ahqceaZkQla4sG1ZV96GGg

• Learned to use Google Analytical Tools.

Excel Module Boot Camp

Career and Placement Center - CPC, North South University

- Attend Boot camp organized by NSU-CPC conducted by Mr. Hasan A. Mamun, Lecturer at NSU
- Acquired advance Excel knowledge

General Member, Associate Information System- Club

North South University

• Volunteered with 40+ team members as security in charge at Club Carnival

EDUCATION

2014-2019	BBA (Bachelor of Business Administration)
	North South University, Bashundhara, Dhaka
	 Major in Management Information System (MIS)
2011 - 2013	HSC (Higher Secondary Certificate)
	Dhaka Commerce Collage, Mirpur, Dhaka
	• Business Studies (3rd subject Statistics, 4th subject Computer Studies)
	• GPA: 4.46
2009 - 2011	SSC (Secondary School Certificate)
	Mohammadpur Model School and Collage
	Business Studies
	• GPA: 4.50

SKILL AND EXPERTISE

Interpersonal Skills

- Fast learner with positive attitude.
- Able to cope with high stress situations.
- Good writing skills.

- Honest and reliable.
- Can work within a team and alone as well.
- Treat work as responsibility.

Technical Skills

Software	Basic	Moderate	Advance
Cisco Packet Tracer			✓
MySQL		✓	
MS Office			✓
JavaScript SDK	√		
Google Analytics tools		✓	
Stata-SE 12		✓	
Notepad++(web design)HTTP+CSS		✓	
WordPress	✓		
knowledge of OS			✓